# **OKORO GODWIN CHINEDU**

16, ABATA CLOSE SARI IGAMMU Lagos State

EMAIL: chinedugodwin300@yahoo.com

Tel: 08062850763

### PERSONAL DATA.

Nationality: Nigerian 25<sup>th</sup> Jan 1991 Date of Birth:

State of Origin: Abia

Local Government Area: Arochukwu

**Marital Status:** Single Gender: Male

Religion: Christianity

## **CAREER SUMMARY**

A statistical analyst and a Market Research Analyst, professional I.T personnel and frontend web designer with a certification from (freecodecamp.org), Online conducting/sales Admin expert with a certificate from GOOGLE, recently took an Android course with GOOGLE AFRICA DEVELOPER SCHOLARSHIP in conjunction with ANDELA and PLURALSIGHT which will earn me a certification in Android and currently working with Outcess Solution as a Software developer and Microsoft Azure Developer.

## SKILL/KEY ATTRIBUTES

- > Organizational, leadership and project management skill demonstrated in dominion leadership instituted.
- Excellent technical skills and practical experience on information and communication technology.
- ➤ Analytical skill coupled with various I.T diploma degrees.
- > Good presentational and mass communication skills demonstrated during my NYSC year in kebbi state on cleaning and personal hygiene.
- ➤ Knowledgeable on computer programming with an ongoing course on PluralSight.
- ➤ Online conducting/sales Admin expert with a certificate from GOOGLE as a Digital Marketer.

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

JUMIA	2016 - 2018
➤ Active work as an online sales Administrator.	
<ul> <li>Intensive training on sales delivering, consulting,</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>Customer care and all round sales.</li> </ul>	
➤ Federal Government college	2018 - 2019
<ul> <li>Economics, Computer science and I.T personnel</li> </ul>	
> Starlight college	2019 - 2020
<ul> <li>Economics, Computer science and I.T personnel</li> </ul>	
Outcess Solution	2021 - date
<ul> <li>Software Developer and Azure Developer</li> </ul>	

# **EDUCATIONAL**

Abia state university uturu abia State B.sc (Hons) in statistics (Second Class Division)	2010 – 2014
Great trinity college kirikiri town Lagos	2001 - 2007
West African Senior School Certificate	
Diamond international school Lagos	1995 - 2001
First School Leaving Testimonial	
National youth service corps -	2018 - 2019

# **OTHER CERTIFICATION**

- Front End Responsive web Designer (freecodecamp.org) 2019
- ➤ D.L.I (dominion leadership institute) 2012
- ➤ (Diploma) IT information technology 2013
- ➤ (Diploma) Business computing 2018
- ➤ SOLO LEARN certificates in (HTML, CSS, PHP, JAVA SRICPT, SQL)
- ➤ Google Digital Marketing 2019

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Web designer, Computer skills, Computer fundamentals, internet applications, Microsoft office word, Microsoft office 365, Excel, Microsoft office, Power point, networking software And Pc Maintenances.

#### REFEREES

Dr. Ogbonnaya Nkwola Nigeria Police Headquarters Abuja 08163253632

Mrs. Akunna Onyenaucheya Niger Delta University Teaching Hospital (NDUTH) Okolobiri Bayelsa State. 08030580070